{
    "id": "9184ec6401bc41e1acefdc9e8eed9346",
    "title": "If Or Whether",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I am not sure …………………… . I will have the time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whether",
                "if",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "40e2da450333421fa8d9fc3235268b62"
        },
        {
            "question": "She asked me ………………… I was working.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fa6276404cff4468ac1b625710edcd59"
        },
        {
            "question": "We discussed ………………… . we should throw a party to celebrate the occasion.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whether",
                "if",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "680cd4e5b6264ae4a2d8af42356af97e"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… . she will me recognize me I am not sure.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Whether",
                "If",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9eb7d5455761415b93fac6f1bdc28fcd"
        },
        {
            "question": "There was a big argument about …………………. she should resign.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whether",
                "if",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "20a76288bb1445abb9be979d101ca483"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t decide …………………….. to go on a diet or not.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whether",
                "if",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6da9e549db0f4f918a1fcbb507e841fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................... she can get along with your mother is another matter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Whether",
                "If",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "343f074f2e63424da5e45270be91505d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked me ............................................ I had ever been to Europe.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whether",
                "if",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d459fb114e5c49f989e568026a75cfe5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know ....................................... she will come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whether",
                "if",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7c7235462edc41d0a8303f7197a7f6f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Janet is going to marry Charles ............................................ she likes it or not.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whether",
                "if",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "15898129a89b404ebb69510e25f7383f"
        }
    ]
}